A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, William J. Ronan, Series 29 FA371
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arthur Levitt Clippings, 1959-1966; 3; 1 Cubic Feet
  - Background Information (Box 48, Folder 532)
    Document explaining procedure regarding collection of newspaper clippings, "over 1,300 clippings were sorted, numbered consecutively and placed into the following eight categories: Politics, Local Government, Taxation, Financing, Legislature, Audit and Control, Education, Miscellaneous."
  - Master Reference Sheets (Box 48, Folder 533)
    Document, listed by year, detailing notable clippings in the collection.
  - Politics, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 534)
  - Politics, 1960 (Box 48, Folder 535)
  - Politics, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 536)
  - Politics, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 537)
  - Politics, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 538)
  - Politics, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 539)
  - Politics, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 540)
  - Politics, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 541)
  - Local Government, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 542)
  - Local Government, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 543)
  - Local Government, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 544)
  - Local Government, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 545)
  - Local Government, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 546)
  - Local Government, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 547)
  - Local Government, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 548)
  - Local Government, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 549)
  - Taxation, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 550)
  - Taxation, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 551)
  - Taxation, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 552)
  - Taxation, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 553)
  - Taxation, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 554)
  - Taxation, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 555)
  - Taxation, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 556)
  - Taxation, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 557)
  - Financing, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 558)
  - Financing, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 559)
  - Financing, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 560)
  - Financing, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 561)
  - Financing, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 562)
  - Financing, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 563)
  - Financing, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 564)
  - Financing, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 565)
  - Legislature, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 566)
  - Legislature, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 567)
  - Legislature, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 568)
  - Legislature, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 569)
  - Legislature, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 570)
  - Legislature, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 571)
  - Legislature, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 572)
  - Legislature, 1966 (Box 49, Folder 573)
  - Audit and Control, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 574)
  - Audit and Control, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 575)
  - Audit and Control, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 576)
  - Audit and Control, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 577)
  - Audit and Control, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 578)
  - Audit and Control, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 579)
  - Audit and Control, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 580)
  - Audit and Control, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 581)
  - Education, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 582)
  - Education, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 583)
  - Education, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 584)
  - Education, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 585)
  - Education, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 586)
  - Education, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 587)
  - Education, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 588)
  - Education, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 589)
  - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 590)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 591)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 592)
  - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 593)
  - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 50, Folder 594)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 595)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 596)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 597)
- Legislation, 1964; 4; 2 Cubic Feet
  This subseries contains a partial selection of legislative proposals submitted to Nelson A. Rockefeller. It contains copies of memoranda explaining Governor Rockefeller's reasoning for either vetoing or approving a particular piece of legislation. Also found in this subseries are legislative proposals for specific state agencies or departments for 1964.
  - 1964 Veto Messages #1-53 (Box 50, Folder 598)
    Memorandum from Governor Rockefeller added to legislation returned to the New York State Legislature after being vetoed by him.
  - 1964 Veto Messages #54-99 (Box 50, Folder 599)
  - 1964 Veto Messages #100-180 (Box 50, Folder 600)
  - 1964 Veto Messages #181-249 (Box 51, Folder 601)
  - 1964 Veto Messages #250-311 (Box 51, Folder 602)
  - 1964 Veto Messages #312-352 (Box 51, Folder 603)
  - 1964 Chapter Numbers (Box 51, Folder 604)
    Press releases summarizing changes to New York State Law approved by Governor Rockefeller.
  - 1964 Approval Messages #1-47 (Box 51, Folder 605)
    Memorandum from Governor Rockefeller added to legislation returned to the New York State Legislature after being approved by him.
  - 1963 Departmental Legislation Drafts (Box 51, Folder 606)
    Legislation pertaining to specific New York State Departments or Agencies, with comments on status of bill.
  - 1962 Departmental Legislation Drafts (Box 51, Folder 607)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments (Box 52, Folder 608)
    Suggested legislation pertaining to specific New York State Departments or Agencies.
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Correction (Box 52, Folder 609)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - General Services (Box 52, Folder 610)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Health (Box 52, Folder 611)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Conservation (Box 52, Folder 612)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Housing (Box 52, Folder 613)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - State Commission for Human Rights (Box 52, Folder 614)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Insurance (Box 52, Folder 615)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Insurance (Box 52, Folder 616)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Department of Agriculture and Markets (Box 52, Folder 617)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Banking (Box 52, Folder 618)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Budget (Box 53, Folder 619)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Civil Defense (Box 53, Folder 620)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Civil Service (Box 53, Folder 621)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - State (Box 53, Folder 622)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - State Police (Box 53, Folder 623)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Investigation Commission (Box 53, Folder 624)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Labor (Box 53, Folder 625)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Division for Youth (Box 53, Folder 626)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Commerce (Box 53, Folder 627)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Public Service Commission (Box 53, Folder 628)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Public Works (Box 53, Folder 629)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Social Welfare (Box 53, Folder 630)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Space and Atomic Development (Box 54, Folder 631)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Taxation and Finance (Box 54, Folder 632)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Thruway Authority (Box 54, Folder 633)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Division of Veterans Affairs (Box 54, Folder 634)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Local Government (Box 54, Folder 635)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Mental Hygiene (Box 54, Folder 636)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Military and Naval Affairs (Box 54, Folder 637)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Motor Vehicles (Box 54, Folder 638)
  - 1964 Proposed Legislation by Departments - Parole (Box 54, Folder 639)
- Speeches and Statements, 1963; 5; 0.4 Cubic Feet
  The subseries is arranged chronologically.
  This small subseries contains a portion of Governor Rockefeller's public statements. It is not clear why only one particular year is represented here.
  - February, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 640)
    Transcripts and press releases of Governor Rockefeller's public remarks.
  - March, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 641)
  - April, 1963 (Box 54, Folder 642)
  - May, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 643)
  - June, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 644)
  - July, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 645)
  - August, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 646)
  - September, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 647)
  - October, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 648)
  - November, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 649)
  - December, 1963 (Box 55, Folder 650)
- General Correspondence, 1959-1966; 6; 2.2 Cubic Feet
  Subseries 6 is arranged alphabetically by the last name of the correspondent.
  This subseries contains general correspondence to and from William Ronan in his capacity as Secretary to the Governor. This material tends to be invitations to various events or information on pertinent issues.
  - A (Box 55, Folder 651)
  - B (Box 55, Folder 652)
  - C (Box 56, Folder 653)
  - D (Box 56, Folder 654)
  - E (Box 56, Folder 655)
  - F (Box 56, Folder 656)
  - G (Box 56, Folder 657)
  - H (Box 56, Folder 658)
  - Invitations, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 659)
    Invitations that were extended to Ronan, not to Governor Rockefeller.
  - Invitations, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 660)
  - Invitations, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 661)
  - Invitations, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 662)
  - Invitations, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 663)
  - Invitations, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 664)
  - Invitations, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 665)
  - Invitations, January-June, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 666)
  - Invitations, January-June, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 667)
  - Invitations, July-December, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 668)
  - Invitations, July-December, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 669)
  - I (Box 58, Folder 670)
  - J (Box 58, Folder 671)
  - K (Box 58, Folder 672)
  - L (Box 59, Folder 673)
  - L (Box 59, Folder 674)
  - M (Box 59, Folder 675)
  - M (Box 59, Folder 676)
  - N (Box 59, Folder 677)
  - O (Box 59, Folder 678)
  - P (Box 60, Folder 679)
  - R (Box 60, Folder 680)
  - S (Box 60, Folder 681)
  - S (Box 60, Folder 682)
  - T (Box 60, Folder 683)
  - V (Box 60, Folder 684)
  - W (Box 60, Folder 685)
  - W (Box 60, Folder 686)
  - Y (Box 60, Folder 687)
  - Z (Box 60, Folder 688)